Everything starts with these guys coming
out of college.
These guys are just starting their NFL
journey and
and I I feel really good about all of
them. The Green Bay Packers select
Brandon Ceaser.
He's a big-time explosive athlete.
He's very young. We think his best
football is ahead of him. We think he's
got so much more left in the tank. He's
explosive and physical.
Chris McLellan, defensive tackle,
Missouri. There's nowhere to go.
Thrown down by Chris McLellan.
The combination of being able to play
the nose and actually rush the passer
and that was that what set him apart for
us.
D-Line Dennis Sutton, the edge rusher
from Penn State. Klubnik in trouble and
D-Line Dennis Sutton wraps him up and
tucks it.
I just think he's got so much in front
of him as far as his best football goes.
It's going to be fun to watch those guys
compete.
You can never have enough competition.
Those guys, you know, coming in can
compete for playing time. Certainly they
got to compete to make the roster first
and foremost.
I think we got great value. The board
held strong, brought in guys that we
truly valued [music] and wanted here to
be a part of our program. These guys I
think are going to be really good
additions to our locker room. I think
they'll help us.